OpenJDK performance primarily so i've
OpenJDK的性能主要是因为
been doing a little bit over the last
在过去做了一点
couple of years some tuning of our
几年来我们的一些调整
startup of the bass openjdk experience
低音openjdk体验的启动
before I start lying
在我开始撒谎之前
I have to show you this one and then
我要给你看一下
let's let's go
让我们走吧
so the startup challenges that we
因此，创业挑战了我们
experience as as Java users and and JVM
具有Java用户和JVM的经验
developers are manifold and the open air
开发商是多方面的，露天的
decay is optimized for peak performance
衰减针对峰值性能进行了优化
and recently we'd said GC and others you
最近我们说GC和其他人
know low low latency and startup and
知道低延迟和启动
footprint has always been these kind of
足迹一直是这类的
nice to have things that you kind of
很高兴拥有您喜欢的东西
expect in client settings but the client
期望在客户端设置中，但是客户端
VM has been drifting away from from open
虚拟机一直在远离开放
JDK
JDK
interest for some time so startup is
感兴趣了一段时间，所以启动是
something that is often drawing and
经常画画的东西
drawing the shortest straw' when it
画最短的稻草
comes to what to optimize what to fix
谈到如何优化修复
for and the nature of the beast and is
对于兽的本质
that you're adding features you're
您正在添加功能
adding new new cool things that optimize
添加可以优化的新功能
you make you make optimization to see to
您使您进行优化以查看
you know make optimization to some
你知道要优化一些
library it adds bloat
库增加膨胀
it adds you know death by a thousand cut
它增加了你知道死亡减少一千
to to the open JDK experience so over
到开放式JDK体验到此为止
six seven eight and especially maybe
六七八，尤其是也许
nine you've seen small small additions
九，你已经看到了小小的补充
of little little things that are in
里面的小东西
getting run at startup or every time you
在启动时或每次您运行时
boot straps and something that adds you
靴带和一些可以增加你的东西
know you typically don't see see them
知道你通常看不到他们
but they do add up over time also in
但随着时间的推移，它们的确会累加
recent I was almost saying decades but
最近我差不多要说几十年了，但是
years we've been adding more and more
几年来我们一直在增加
dynamic setup things Don hiding I was
动态设置东西唐躲我
here talking about Indian comedy earlier
早些时候在这里谈论印度喜剧
and that's kind of the trend that we are
这就是我们的趋势
on to use
继续使用
dynamic bootstraps for more and more
动态引导程序越来越多
things and those things well they're not
东西和那些东西好，他们不是
for free especially not for from a
是免费的，特别是不是从
starter point of view also for from a
初学者的观点也从
footprint point of view so and we're
足迹的观点，所以我们
going to add more of those probably so
要增加更多的可能是这样
how do we deal with that that conundrum
我们如何应对这个难题
to try and keep at least startup stable
尝试至少保持启动稳定
or improving our time without blocking
或改善我们的时间而不受阻碍
nice feature improvements using Indy and
使用Indy和
other features so well before you before
其他功能在您之前
you optimize anything you have to ask
您可以优化您需要问的任何问题
yourself why why bother well there's
你自己，为什么要打扰那里
been a there's been a range of interests
有一个兴趣范围
in making Java faster to start up and
使Java更快地启动以及
anything from people you know picking up
你认识的人的任何东西
languages just you write some CLI tool
语言，只需编写一些CLI工具
or your your function as a service
或您的服务职能
vendor wants to cut a few mic
供应商想削减一些麦克风
milliseconds off of your service times
您的服务时间减少了毫秒
when you're bootstrapping a new VM every
当您每次引导一个新的VM时
time you're servicing in a request which
您为请求服务的时间
seems a little bit high on the overhead
开销似乎有点高
side and of course you have you know
方面，当然你知道
legacy efforts in the open UDK community
UDK开放社区中的传统工作
you have embedded and client vm etc and
您已经嵌入了客户端虚拟机等
we're mostly focusing on on the server
我们主要专注于服务器
VM today so how do we make the server VM
今天的虚拟机，那么我们如何使服务器虚拟机
encompass and you know accommodate some
包围，你知道容纳一些
of the use cases previously done in
先前在
different optimization different
不同的优化不同
repositories well and you know the other
仓库很好，你知道另一个
reasons are more maybe personal I like
原因可能更多是我喜欢的个人原因
to keep fighting the misconception that
继续对抗误解
Java is slow and I like to improve the
Java很慢，我想改善
quality of life of my own
我自己的生活质量
development experience you know every
你们都知道的开发经验
every 10 millisecond we can cut away
每隔10毫秒我们就可以消除
from startup mix you know our testing
通过启动组合，您知道我们的测试
environment from half an hour faster so
环境要快半个小时，所以
there's that
有那个
when it comes to startup techniques
关于启动技术
there are a lot of high level things
有很多高级的东西
that have been you know feature iced
一直以来你都知道功能冰
over the years going way back you have
几年过去了
Stata sharing Sidious it was incepted
Stata分享Sidious被接受
back in in the client vm mostly first
回到客户端虚拟机首先
implemented for Windows 2 to make
为Windows 2实现
applets start faster why is it still a
小程序启动更快，为什么它仍然是
thing well someone realized that there
事情很好，有人意识到
we can we can adapt this and use this on
我们可以适应并在
server class VMs expanded to include the
服务器类VM已扩展为包括
application application classes themself
应用程序将自己分类
so it was kind of built as a commercial
所以它有点像商业广告
feature for for Oracle VMs to support of
Oracle VM支持的功能
logic servers with application class
具有应用程序类的逻辑服务器
data sharing and this commercial feature
数据共享和此商业功能
open sourced fully in 11 so now we can
在11中完全开源，所以现在我们可以
use application class data sharing and
使用应用程序类数据共享和
it's kind of cool you you had it run it
你让它运行起来很酷
for your application and it can cut up
为您的应用程序，它可以削减
to 50 percent of your startup if you're
如果是
lucky your mileage may vary the aut
幸运的是，您的里程可能会有所不同
effort in Java 9 added an experimental
Java 9中的努力增加了实验性
experimental ahead of time compiler
实验性的提前编译器
coming out of the draw effort so it's a
从平局努力中出来的
girl based compiler shipped with open
基于女孩的编译器附带开放
indicated it allows you to pre compile
表明它允许您预编译
your yoga classes to an 880 shared
您的瑜伽课要共享880
library which has a little bit of a
有一点点的图书馆
mixed mixed bag of results but the
混合结果混合袋，但
benefit is your 80 archives are loaded
好处是您的80个档案已加载
in and it doesn't really affect your
并不会真正影响您
application other than that it adds and
除了它添加的应用程序和
message to whatever to your code cache
消息发送到代码缓存中的任何内容
button
纽扣
well the peak performance won't do guys
最好的表现不会
too much but I'm not going to talk much
太多了，但我不想多说
about äôt and then there are other more
关于äôt，然后还有其他
intrusive and experimental features like
侵入性和实验性功能，例如
the well what you can do with jailing to
那么你可以通过监狱来做
cut away things from your runtime images
从运行时映像中删除内容
or compress them or do other things
或压缩它们或做其他事情
basically enables to write plugins that
基本上可以编写插件
would do that could theoretically do a
从理论上讲可以做到
lot of the things that you are doing
您正在做的很多事情
today with
今天与
agents but you can do them ahead of time
代理商，但您可以提前完成
in as a j-link
作为J链接
pipeline so it's something that links
管道，所以它可以链接
your image ahead of time so if you're
提前显示您的图像，如果
shipping image you can do that ahead of
运送图片，您可以提前完成
time native image is also something that
时间原生图像也是
is on the radar but it's not included in
在雷达上，但不包含在其中
this talk so it's it's a girl VM effort
这个演讲是女孩VM的努力
to compile your java application down
编译您的Java应用程序
into with close to world assumptions
接近世界的假设
down to a single binary so it's kind of
下降到一个二进制文件，所以有点
cuts most of the avium after the picture
图片后切掉大部分的禽蛋
and gives you a runtime image so the
并为您提供了运行时映像，因此
efforts in this is it's out of scope for
这方面的努力超出了
for this talk but it's fun things to to
对于这个演讲，但是很有趣
look at if you're really just looking
看看你是否真的在看
for something that starts fast runs with
对于快速启动的东西
a minimal binary size and such but I'm
最小的二进制大小，但我
well not looking at those things right
好吧，不要看那些东西对
now I'm more looking from perspective of
现在我更多地是从
you know OpenJDK how do we make java has
你知道OpenJDK我们如何使java有
everyone knows it start a little bit
大家都知道它开始了一点
faster because reasons so I usually
更快，因为原因，所以我通常
start with well with hello world which
从你好世界开始
is everyone's favorite startup micro
是每个人最喜欢的创业公司
benchmark since since at least 95 and
自至少95岁以来
when it comes to well what do you mean
说到你是什么意思
we'd start up it's a little bit
我们会开始一点
ill-defined but most most people kind of
定义不明确，但大多数人都这样
they run hello world and they clock it
他们跑世界，他们计时
with with you spend time or whatever and
与您共度时光或其他
say like oh my JVM started in 100
像哦，我的JVM从100开始
milliseconds well I didn't only start it
毫秒好，我不仅开始了
it also ran its course and then it shut
它也跑了，然后关闭了
everything down and all those you know
一切都下来，所有你知道的
handoffs and synchronization with the OS
操作系统的切换和同步
adds a lot of time depending on for
会增加很多时间，具体取决于
example if your concurrent GC cycle has
如果您的并发GC周期具有
already started and one or whichever
已经开始，一个或任何一个
collector you're running might be
您正在运行的收集器可能是
blocking for for some some level of some
某种程度的阻塞
amount of time so if you really want you
时间量，所以如果你真的想要你
to measure startup you should you have
衡量启动的条件
some way to well maybe some external
某种方式可能会很好
that recognizes when your application is
识别您的应用程序何时
actually up and running for example when
实际启动并运行，例如
when the hello world print is printed on
当您好打印世界
the only terminal whatever and times
无论何时何地，唯一的航站楼
that section but let's ignore let's
该部分，但让我们忽略让我们
ignore that and just run everything free
忽略它，然后免费运行所有内容
from here on out in this talk run
从这里开始
everything from start to finish if
从头到尾的一切，如果
you're running bigger things might be
你正在做更大的事情可能是
more important to define startup as the
将启动定义为
initial face so I really started looking
最初的面孔，所以我真的开始寻找
at startup in the lead up to JDK 9 and
在启动之前，一直到JDK 9和
well the module system that everyone
好每个人的模块系统
loves some places these days came with
喜欢这些天来的一些地方
some level of initial overheads German
一定程度的初始间接费用德语
nein regressed well wasn't too much on
尼宁回归得还不错
my workstation but maybe from if I saw
我的工作站，但也许是从我看到的
90 milliseconds startup times on startup
启动时90毫秒的启动时间
times on Java 8 I could see them grow to
在Java 8上的时代我可以看到它们成长为
Java well in Java 9 to 110 milliseconds
Java在Java 9到110毫秒之间
you don't want to see the early access
您不想看到抢先体验
bills of jigsaw that I started mission
我开始执行任务的拼图游戏
when I started measuring this they were
当我开始测量它们时
probably in like in 250 300 millisecond
大概在250300毫秒内
range but the module system itself kind
范围，但模块系统本身种类
of the project unfolded and folded
项目的展开和折叠
various things into a linked plug-ins
将各种东西放入链接的插件中
and did a lot of things to cut cut away
做了很多事情要切掉
a lot of the overhead before we released
我们发布之前的大量开销
gamma 9 but we also saw progressions in
伽玛9，但我们也看到了
yeoman I'm due to you know the
我是由于你知道
accumulation of features in the VM and
VM中的功能积累和
elsewhere over three years and this this
在其他地方超过三年，这
comparison adds a few milliseconds
比较会增加几毫秒
simply due to the fact that we made g1
仅仅因为我们制造了g1
default and we added support segments
默认，我们添加了支持细分
the code cache basically separate c1 and
代码缓存基本上将c1和
c2 generated code into different areas
c2将代码生成到不同的区域
whereas previously they were intermixed
而以前它们是混合在一起的
but the separation themselves added a
但是分离本身增加了一个
little bit of indirection which nine
一点点间接哪九
cost some
花费一些
methods to be become virtual methods and
成为虚拟方法的方法，以及
that a little bit of overhead there so
那边有一点开销
that various very small things adding up
各种小事加起来
JVM CI at the to support growl as an
JVM CI支持将咆哮作为
experimental compiler in JAMA nine adds
JAMA中的实验性编译器九个新增
a little bit of overhead to everyone
每个人的开销
else as well things like that
还有其他类似的事情
my favorite regression was due to the VM
我最喜欢的回归是由于虚拟机
flag constraint checking that was added
标志约束检查已添加
in Java nine which adds on the order of
在Java 9中，其顺序为
like fifteen million instructions being
就像一千五百万条指令
retired on every VN start just to check
在每个VN开始时退役只是为了检查
if your if your command-line arguments
如果您的命令行参数
are within range of the allowed numbers
在允许的数字范围内
so that was the case when there were no
所以当没有
command line flags at all so yeah I
命令行标志都没有，所以我
started there fixing that one and we
开始在那里修理那个，我们
started looking at you know we kept
开始看着你知道我们一直
looking and I've been looking at
看，我一直在看
optimizing unique so for well over a
优化独特性，因此
year but for you over ten we kept
一年，但为您保留了十多年
fighting the technical depth and that we
争取技术深度，我们
had built up in German nein ja well we
在德国的nein ja建立了我们
fixed numerous of these small library
修复了许多小型图书馆
and other runtime optimizations like the
和其他运行时优化，例如
VM flag checking cat so it cuts away you
VM标志检查猫，这样可以割舍您
know my fractions of milliseconds for
知道我的毫秒数
each such infraction
每个这样的违反
other other other other optimizations
其他其他其他优化
came from you know others like Thomas
来自你认识像托马斯这样的人
Quetzal doing g1 and startup and
Quetzal做g1并启动和
footprint improvements for for some of
某些产品的占地面积改善
our big customers that help helps also
我们的大客户也有帮助
the nominal and you know early startup
标称的，你知道早起
of of Java for everyone there were you
适用于所有人的Java语言
know improvements to CD s starting to
知道CD的改进开始
add support for previous or having
添加对先前或具有的支持
constituents or whatever so JDK tell 10
组成部分或JDK告诉10
on my machine
在我的机器上
we actually was able to get back to
我们实际上能够回到
break even with with Java Java 8 I'm not
与Java达到收支平衡Java 8我不是
sure were there were small incremental
确定有小的增量
regressions
回归
on some measures but no not on hello
在某些措施上，但不是没有
world mostly most of the time there were
世界上大多数时候
there were the regressions there were
有回归
seen on with larger things but most of
看到更大的东西，但大多数
them were resolved during the eight
他们在八年中得到解决
updates so eight updates kind of started
更新，所以开始了八种更新
improving trend as well right well the
以及改善趋势
project to keep improving startup kind
不断改进创业项目的项目
of trapped on into into JDK 11 because
之所以陷入JDK 11中，是因为
well was slated to be a long term
预计将是长期的
support early so there was still
尽早提供支持，所以仍然
interesting keeping keeping these things
保持这些东西很有趣
rolling we got a little bit of you know
滚动，我们有一点你知道
unintended helped by the fact that just
意想不到的帮助
removing a number of modules helps
删除一些模块有助于
improve startup at least in the
至少在
framework or in the context of 11 so
框架或在11的上下文中
getting rid of java xml bind and other
摆脱Java xml绑定和其他
other other couple of modules that
其他两个模块
bring-bring didn't spark yuri enough to
带入并没有激发出尤里
be kept in the jdk because they can be
保留在jdk中，因为它们可以
you know in pulled in as as dependencies
你知道作为依赖项拉入
and probably you should usually you want
通常你应该想要
to you know i don't know how many
你知道我不知道有多少
enterprise systems I've been in where
我去过的企业系统
where you had the dependency on Jack's
你对杰克的依赖
be 2.1 but your jdk of choice ships with
是2.1，但您选择的jdk附带
2.0 which someone else has in dependency
别人依赖的2.0
on and you have this lib xed path you
继续，您有此lib固定路径
know all that fun enjoy that that the
知道所有的乐趣享受
module system wanted to get you know get
模块系统想要让您知道获得
to the bottom of and kind of succeeded
归根到底
but to the grief and anointment of lots
而是很多的悲伤和恩膏
of deployers anyhow library
部署程序库
optimizations continue as well but
优化也在继续，但
didn't you know we kept a nice downward
你不知道我们保持良好的下降
trajectory I would say and we kept on
我会说的轨迹，我们继续
digging for for Java 12 these are
为Java 12挖掘这些是
slightly old slides so I should probably
幻灯片稍旧，所以我应该
remove the question mark in the title
删除标题中的问号
here we'll kept
在这里，我们继续
kept improving things c.d.s can now
不断改进CD现在可以
sterilize default model graphs so we are
消毒默认模型图，所以我们
we're where we have the facilities in
我们在这里拥有设施
place to kind of not run the Java code
不运行Java代码的地方
to do a lot of the things that we do
做很多我们要做的事情
during module setup it at all we're just
在模块设置过程中，我们只是
loading the result of it from the CD s
从CD加载结果
archive so we we don't have to run you
存档，因此我们不必运行您
know quite a substantial chunk of Java
知道很多Java
code during bootstrap to set things up
引导过程中的代码以进行设置
and we we have a toolbox now to keep on
我们现在有一个工具箱可以继续
doing that for all of the things that we
为我们所有的事情做
are you know doing every time we're
你知道我们每次都在做吗
starting like creating locales and
开始像创建语言环境和
character datasets that are so we can
这样的字符数据集
probably keep on doing there we have a
可能会继续这样做，我们有一个
nice new tool set even though we are not
不错的新工具集，即使我们不是
using it as extensively as we could but
尽可能广泛地使用它，但是
good good good place to keep keep on
好保持继续的好地方
digging all these numbers are with C
用C挖掘所有这些数字
that CD s enabled and a new thing that
CD已启用，还有新东西
might help people pulling in and testing
可能会帮助人们进行测试
on CD over twelve is that CD essence now
在CD上十二岁以上的是CD本质
enabled by default you don't have to go
默认情况下启用，您不必走
through the hoops of dumping or whatever
通过倾销或任何其他形式
is you'll have a base archive ready set
您将准备好基本存档吗
that will always work and there's been
那将永远有效，并且已经
improvements to make sure that even if
进行改进以确保即使
the CD historico wasn't you know
CD历史记录不是吗
generated for the exact heap sizes etc
为确切的堆大小生成等
because it it modulates a little bit a
因为它调制了一点
few of the things it it kind of allows
它允许的一些事情
for in a very very quick patching of
对于非常非常快速的修补
these archives into memory so so it
这些档案存储到内存中，所以
should always being a substantial start
应该永远是一个重要的开始
up improvement yeah of course as in an
是的，当然，
unreleased our local regressions that we
未发布我们的局部回归
are looking into but you know yeah so
正在调查，但你知道，是的，所以
another view of this is to measure the
另一个观点是衡量
amount of bytecode that we execute
我们执行的字节码数量
during startup and the number of byte
启动过程中的字节数
codes we execute kind of shifts
我们执行某种转换的代码
depending on what kind of machine we are
取决于我们是哪种机器
on if you have a machine with
如果您有一台机器
well this oh sorry
好吧，对不起
this light is comparing if you run an
如果您运行
interpreter only with out-of-the-box
开箱即用的口译员
experience so you'll see that Jade
经验，所以你会看到玉
threads quickly take all the other code
线程快速获取所有其他代码
that you're running during bootstrap and
您在引导过程中正在运行
runs them through yet optimized system
通过尚未优化的系统运行它们
away so we see that the number of byte
走开，所以我们看到字节数
codes executed kind of shifts
代码执行的移位
dramatically and dynamically with each
每个人都充满活力
release but yeah let's so and well the
释放，但是是的，让我们做得很好
gist of it is that in Java 9 the the raw
要点是，在Java 9中
amount about code needed to bootstrap a
有关引导程序所需代码的数量
JVM increased by 9x and then we started
JVM增加了9倍，然后我们开始
you know cutting away at the number of
你知道减少了
robot codes needed to execute in each
每个机器人都需要执行的机器人代码
subsequent release and yet threads are
后续版本，但线程
you know starting faster or starting up
你知道开始更快还是开始
faster in the in the bootstrap cycle so
在引导周期中更快
so it it well in the end we execute less
这样很好，最后我们减少执行
bytecode even though we're doing more in
字节码，即使我们在
in the bootstrap than before before
在引导中比以前
you're late anyhow you'll see different
无论如何你都会迟到
slightly different numbers maybe on
可能略有不同的数字
systems depending on how many course I
系统取决于我的课程数
mean it threads you can throw what the
意味着它可以把你扔的东西
problem of you know optimizing away
你的问题知道优化
otherwise interpreted Java code for
否则解释为
example the top top here is my
例如，这里的顶部是我的
workstation which is a dual socket
双插座工作站
workstation it quickly sees you know the
工作站，它很快就会看到您知道
improvements from from from 9 to 12 lead
从9改进为12
lead into and you know we are we are now
导致，你知道我们是我们现在
starting and running faster than Java 8
比Java 8更快地启动和运行
but I don't I don't see I kind of break
但我不，我看不到我有休息
even on my laptop because it has fewer
即使在我的笔记本电脑上，因为它的数量更少
yet threads to to kind of leverage the
但仍想利用
the the improvements that we've done but
我们所做的改进，但是
they're very very even now on Java 13
他们现在在Java 13上都非常非常
anyhow let's move on to lambdas and well
无论如何，让我们继续讨论lambdas
what we since since you have eight when
自从你有八个之后
lambdas were introduced we've kind of
引入了lambdas，我们已经
been cognizant to the fact that
意识到以下事实：
bootstrapping lambdas is kind of heavy
引导lambdas很重
on the on the cost on first or initial
首次或初始费用
initial use so on Java 8 if you take the
最初使用Java 8，如果您使用
simple simplest Java Java lambda
最简单的Java Java lambda
benchmark and and run it you'll see that
进行基准测试并运行它，您将看到
it'll have an overhead of the equivalent
它会有相当的开销
you know legacy in Java code that was a
您知道Java代码中的传统
little bit on the heavy side my
一点沉重的一面我
workstation I could see about 90
我可以看到大约90台工作站
milliseconds we started looking at that
毫秒，我们开始查看
in Java 9 - the way a lot of the
在Java 9中-很多
overheads of these invokedynamic
这些调用动态的开销
the of the lambda meter factory thing so
拉姆达表厂的事情
we cleaned up the implementation a lot
我们清理了很多实施
in the opening decay we wrote a jailing
在开头的衰变中，我们写了一篇jail
plugin that allows for a pre generation
允许预生成的插件
of some of the methyl handles or method
一些甲基手柄或方法
yeah method handle forms like link link
是的，方法处理的形式像链接
lambda forms etcetera there are like the
lambda形式etcetera有像
constituents building blocks off of some
三大要素的构成要素
of the metal handle framework that is
金属手柄框架的
used to implement java.lang invoking in
用于实现java.lang的调用
d and we could cut away like 50% of the
d，我们可以削减50％的
overhead of of lambdas so even though
即使如此，lambda的开销也是如此
then start up in general regressed in
然后一般开始回归
jama 9 as if your application hand one
jama 9好像您的应用程序是一只
or a few lambdas you were actually
或你实际上是几个lambda
improving even on nine
即使在九点上也有所改善
and we kept improving in nine and in ten
而且我们在九点和十点不断改进
as well and then I realized that most of
我也意识到
the method handle adaptive adapter stuff
该方法处理自适应适配器的东西
that we did in in setting up the first
我们在建立第一个
in initial invocation of a lambda was
最初调用lambda是
actually an unnecessary and an artifact
实际上是不必要的和人工的
that we weren't using static type
我们没有使用静态类型
information in the code that called the
代码中的信息称为
bootstrap method so we fixed that got
引导方法，所以我们修复了
rid of another 75 percent of the Oh
摆脱了另外75％的哦